Dead Man Running is a action, crime, drama film directed by Alex De Rakoff.
A loan shark gives ex-con Nick a period of 24 hours in
order to pay back the money he owes.
Up against it, Nick involves his best mate on a multi-part mission in
order to raise the cash before it's too late for them both
Thigo, played by 50 Cent.
Nick, played by Tamer Hassan.
Bing, played by Danny Dyer.
Jarvis, played by Blake Ritson.
Herself - Featured Burlesque Performer, played by Esmé Bianco.
Frankie, played by Monet Mazur.
Dead Man Running  is a 2009 British crime comedy film directed by Alex De Rakoff, written
by De Rakoff and John Luton, and starring Tamer Hassan and Danny Dyer.
Football players Ashley Cole and Rio Ferdinand served as executive producers.
The tone is emotional and intense.